Hi everybody.
こんにちは
I'll be answering the question, what do you know about our company?.
今日は「弊社について何をご存知ですか」 という質問にお答えします
So before the interview I did a bit of research.
面接の前に 少しリサーチしました
I read articles, I checked out some blog posts.
記事を読んだり ブログの投稿をチェックしたり
I went on the Udacity website and read the about us section and
Udacity のウェブサイトにある 「弊社について」に目を通して
then checked out a few courses in nanodegrees.
Nanodegree のコースを いくつかチェックしました
And what I learned is that Udacity is trying to
そこで私が知ったのは Udacity が人々の学習の形に
change the way that people learn.
変革をもたらそうとしているということです
Before, it was thought that education is something that happens at the first
教育というは成人期の 最初の 4 年間に積むもので
four years of adulthood, and stops right there.
そこで終了するというのが これまでの通念でした
The rest of your career you don't need to worry about it.
その後のキャリアは心配無用 というわけです
But, of course, the world is changing much, much, much too rapidly for
しかし当然のことながら そんな通念がまかり通らないくらいのスピードで
that to still be the case.
世界は変化を遂げています
Today people have to learn throughout their careers.
キャリア全体を通じた 継続学習は今や必須です
So what Udacity is doing is trying to change education and
そこで Udacity が 試みようとしているのが
turn it into something that people can do throughout their lives.
教育に変革をもたらし 誰もが生涯続けられる形に教育を変えることです
It's an education that can happen when people want it and how people want it.
つまり、必要なとき 必要な方法で提供される教育です
And it also is there to help people get new jobs.
教育は転職の一助にもなります
Udacity also has the opportunity to teach people a new way simply
オンラインベースの Udacity なら
because this education is happening online.
新しい方法を効率よく 学習することができます
People have computers in front of them which means that you can go much beyond
コンピューターで ビデオやクイズを活用しながら学習できるため
simply offering videos and quizzes, and you can create totally
従来の枠をはるかに超えた 新たな学習環境が実現します
new educational experiences that not just connect people with material,
また物質だけでなく 人と人が相互につながった
but also connect people with each other.
斬新な学習経験が構築されます
So I think that Udascity is a company that's doing their best
学習の変革に向けて 尽力している Udascity は
to change the way that people learn and I think they're doing it for the better.
より良い未来を実現する 企業だと確信しています
Thanks.
ありがとうございました